[narrator]: In Toronto's
war on crime.
the worst offenders
are pursued by the detectives
of the Specialized Criminal
Investigations Unit.
These are their stories.
[echoing gavel]
[laughter and chatter]
- Loves to cook.
All right.
two or more languages.
[chuckling]
You lot are putting me to shame.
All right. what about
loves live performance?
- Hm.
- Huh. Jim Coer. Peter Buff.
Edwin. we could be twins.
[chuckling]
- Back home. I once did
costume design for
a theatre company in Nairobi.
I. uh. made this tie. actually.
[scoffs]
- All right. Forget twins.
You have way too much time.
[chuckling]
I bet you're proud of your son.
- Would you care to try
Len's famous
date and walnut cookies?
Have fun.
- All right. so.
drinks coffee or tea...
[water running]
- Hey. Adam.
Oof. what happened there?
- Sprained tendon.
Just hit the bag wrong.
- I used to do a bit
of boxing back in the day.
Wrist support is everything.
- Yeah. thanks.
- Hey. Tevin.
- Welcome back. Len.
[intriguing music]
- Wait. a room?
[chuckling]
Babe. it's a den.
It doesn't even have a door.
- Yeah. but I have
a nutribullet.
- I thought that broke.
- Which is why
I need the roommate.
Whoa. Hi.
- You don't tape over
someone's face.
- It's old news. Hazel.
- That doesn't mean
it's yours to cover.
- All right. my bad.
[suspenseful music]
♪ Move to the left
if you have a few left ♪
♪ Slide to the right
'cause I know it ain't right ♪
♪ Drop down low 'cause you
already know that you fly ♪
♪ Jump up
if you're feeling the high ♪
♪ Step to the back
'cause you're never going back ♪
♪ Pump to the front 'cause
you're never gonna front ♪
♪ Boy. now I know
that it's true ♪
♪ It's not me. boy.
it's not me. it's you ♪
[rhythmic music]
- Thanks for bringing me.
- Oh. don't mention it.
I've been where you are.
- It's two doubles.
[glasses thudding]
And. uh... I'm single.
- Uh. leave the kid alone.
[chuckling]
We're gonna find a spot.
- Hey! Are you holding?
- I know. I know.
You drop it. I stack it.
- Davie.
what can I get you to drink?
[police sirens afar]
- What exactly are they saying?
Well. let them spin the story
however they want.
As long as my name
doesn't come up.
[muffled booming club music]
Yeah. all right. thanks.
Keep me posted.
[dispatch over radio]:
Are you there. Webb?
There's a traffic incident
at Church and Wellesley.
[engine starts]
- Webb here.
currently unavailable.
[indistinct shouting]
[club music stops abruptly]
- Hey. take it easy on him.
He just wants to see the show.
- You don't speak to me
about my son.
Let that be your first
and last mistake.
[suspenseful music builds]
- So I said
if she wants a nanny.
she can pay the payroll tax.
[gasping]
- God. Em.
you're. like. the only woman
I know that can't cardio
and gossip at the same time.
[shaky breathing]
[theme music]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Couple of locals were getting
their morning steps in
when they spotted him.
Call came in at 6:30 AM.
[police radios chirping]
- Any other witnesses?
- Canvassing. but nothing yet.
We got a line search underway
to look for the murder weapon.
The assault started
up there on the pathway.
continued down. ended here.
- Blunt force to the head.
Heavy on the trauma.
[exhaling]
- You got a name?
- Len Marsden. 55.
- Cash. credit cards.
looks like it's all here.
- Been working this
neighbourhood for a long time.
Muggings are rare.
Murders... rarer.
- Well. Rosedale's not exactly
a... hotbed of sin.
Quiet. rich.
One of the lowest crime rates
in the country. actually.
Nice gig.
- It was up until this morning.
- Maybe it was a crime
of opportunity.
Killer waited for
the perfect moment.
Strikes hard. then moved on.
- Moved over this way.
A freshly dug hole.
[intriguing music]
- Oh. boy.
- Looks like the killer
was planning on
burying the body.
Maybe something
interrupted them.
- The park lights are on timers.
Set to come on at dusk
and turn off at dawn.
That one's still on.
Its timer must be faulty.
And maybe the attack
happened at night.
Light kicked on and spooked
the killer mid burial.
- Time of death is between
11 PM and two AM last night.
Cause of death. multiple
traumatic blows to the head.
And when I say multiple.
I mean that our victim
took a serious beating.
He was dead
before the final blow
even landed.
- So. serious overkill.
Uh. what'd they use?
- Some blunt baton-like weapon.
- Any signs he fought back?
- None. No defensive wounds.
- It's hard to believe
a man of Len's size
would go down without a fight.
- He didn't defend himself
because he couldn't.
Toxicology turned up
a high blood alcohol level
and a high dose of ketamine.
Both ingested less than
an hour before he died.
- So. essentially.
he was legless
by the time he got
on the path.
- Do we know
what Len was doing
on the path so late
in the first place?
- His apartment's in Rosedale.
Ten-minute walk
from the crime scene.
- So. maybe somebody saw him
drunk. drugged. walking alone.
decided to take advantage.
- Could be.
Or it's just as possible
that somebody wanted him
in that state.
As Bateman says.
look at the size of the guy.
He'd be a lot easier
to handle like that.
- No next of kin.
no financial activity yesterday.
Well. The man had nobody.
and yet half of Rosedale
is calling in.
demanding to know
what happened to him.
- Okay. we'll head to his place.
[sighing]
Build a timeline forward.
Find out why big Len here
didn't make it home last night.
- Remember what they did
to Jamie's son. Levi?
When they caught him
with the neighbour boy.
They dragged him through
their village. Flogged him.
Until he stopped breathing.
- It's not like that here.
- Edwin.
do you think I wanted
to do that last night?
I had to for you.
- Len. Len didn't deserve--
- Never speak that name again.
[echoing gavel]
[papers crumpling]
[sighing]
- Give me something.
Where are you?
[intriguing music]
[sighing]
- Spoke with Len's landlord.
Last time she saw him
was yesterday.
He was pulling out
in his van around noon.
- His van's back
in the parking spot?
- No. actually.
just flagged it with CPIC.
Patrol are watching out for...
What? What'd you find?
- A calendar entry.
Yesterday at noon.
N.H.U.
- N.H.U.
Could be someone's initials?
- No.
New Haven United Church.
- Amen.
- Len was a self-employed
handyman.
I've been contracting him
for years.
He's dependable. quiet.
Always got the job done.
- You two were close.
- Not at first.
He mostly kept to himself.
But. uh. a few years back.
I asked him if he would help
with some renovations.
Pews. benches.
that sort of thing.
And then he was around a lot.
- And did that change things
between the two of you?
- New Haven is a very
inclusive space
and Len could see that.
Soon enough. he was a beloved
member of the congregation.
This is gonna upset
a lot of people.
- Anyone in particular?
Someone that he'd been seeing
a lot more of lately?
- A young man named Edwin.
Uh. Kenyan. newcomer.
They met at a new Canadian tea
recently and got on well.
Edwin stopped by
yesterday to see Len.
They left together around seven.
- Did he mention
where they were going?
- No.
But. strangely.
I got an email this morning
from Edwin's father. Jeremiah.
He asked to be taken off
the church event's mailing list.
I got the sense that...
he wasn't comfortable with
Len and Edwin's friendship.
- Thank you.
[echoing gavel]
I just came
from New Haven Church.
Minister Cade
informed me that. um.
he received a strange
request from you.
Why did you send that email?
- I could not continue
to accept help from a church
that welcomes people like Len.
- Len was just like me.
[heavy breathing]
He understood what it was like
to have a father
who couldn't accept him
for who he was.
- After you and Len left
the church yesterday.
where did you go?
- He knew I was looking
for a queer community
in Toronto.
so he offered to take me
to a drag show.
- I went to this show
to get him.
He was drunk. dancing.
- So what'd you do?
- I raised my voice.
- Is that all?
- Broke some glasses.
I won't deny it.
but no one was hurt.
- My father brought me
straight home
and we've been here ever since.
When. uh.
we left that drag show.
Len was a little drunk.
but very much alive.
- Did you see any drugs?
Ketamine?
- I don't know what that is.
I just wanted to see the show.
- Okay.
Uh. and where was this show?
- Crews & Tangos.
It's a bar in an area Len called
the Gay Village.
[tense music]
Back home.
being gay can get you killed
by your family.
My father is scared
what happened to Len
could happen to me.
But he's not a bad man.
- Father said the. uh.
confrontation wasn't violent
and they left Crews & Tangos
around nine.
- Kid's telling the same story.
He claims they haven't left
the apartment since.
- Da Silva says that Len
had his last drink
and took the drugs
in the hour before he died.
so no earlier than 10 PM.
If their alibi holds--
- Edwin would've been
long gone
before he'd even have
the chance to dose Len.
- So let's find out
who stuck around.
[echoing gavel]
[booming club music]
- Who was Len talking to
after Edwin and his father left?
- I couldn't tell you.
It was drag night.
the place is packed.
I served Len and Edwin
around eight. saw them again
during all the drama.
And didn't pay much attention
to Len after that.
- You know. our pathologist
told us that. uh.
by the time this guy left.
he could barely walk.
So. who was the last
to serve him?
- Any one of the other
bartenders?
Or my manager. Hazel.
She might have stepped in.
She knew Len better than I did.
- And where is she now?
- Upstairs bar.
- One last question.
Do you know where Len
might've found ketamine in here?
- Yeah. no.
But. place like this.
night like that.
wouldn't take much asking.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
[booming bar music continues]
- Cut him off around 10:30.
Len didn't come in
that often. but...
I think after that argument
with that kid's dad.
he overdid it a bit.
Drugs. though. I don't know
where those came from.
- Did you happen to notice
Len hanging out
or leaving with anyone?
- No.
But I was up here bartending
for most of the night.
He was downstairs.
- I noticed a couple of these
posters up the block.
but. uh.
it was a different name.
Omar and. uh. Yusuf.
These yours?
- Yeah. Len and I were gonna go
canvassing in Cabbagetown
this afternoon.
- Hm. the two of you
were searching for these men?
- Yes.
Us along with some others.
That's how we met.
- Did Len know any of these men?
- No.
But the village
is pretty tight-knit.
You know. it's big and small
at the same time.
[Bateman]: And what have
the police turned up?
- Nothing.
They're brown-skinned.
Gay. They're living
on the edge of society.
[shutter clicking]
It's nothing new. though.
The cops in this community
are enforcers.
not protectors.
What happened to Len is awful.
but if it had happened in
the village instead of Rosedale.
who knows how seriously
the local police
would've taken
the investigation?
- So. all these men went missing
from the village
within the last two years?
- Yes.
Pattern's obvious to us.
Even though the cops pretend
like it doesn't mean anything.
- You think the same person's
behind these disappearances.
- You see it. don't you?
[intriguing music swelling]
- Alright. let's say that
the village is on to something.
How does Len Marsden
fit in with this picture?
- Well. he obviously doesn't
match the racial profile.
but he does fit a pattern.
Middle-aged. bearded.
bigger bodied.
All these men self-identified
as bears.
The demography tracks.
- As does the geography.
Omar. Yusuf. and Arjun
were all last seen
within a kilometre
of each other.
And Len was likely drugged
at Crews & Tangos.
which is smack dab in the middle
of that area.
- And if these other
three men are dead.
where are their bodies?
Because Len's body
turned up on that trail.
- We found a shallow grave
at the scene.
We're thinking the killer
intended to bury Len.
but. uh. didn't get the chance
to finish the job.
- And serial killers get caught
when they get sloppy.
This might be
their first slip up.
- All right. put a team
on the Ravine Trail.
Have them search
for other graves
and follow up with whoever
handled the missing men's cases.
[echoing gavel]
- Officer Webb.
how long you've been
running point on the. uh.
village detail?
- Few years now.
Big on outreach.
Boots on the ground.
My team's done
a really good job
at keeping lines
of communication open.
- So. you've heard about this.
uh. serial killer theory?
- Only at every town hall
since last winter.
Really picked up after
Akeem Shadid disappeared.
- Akeem Shadid? I-I don't
remember Hazel mentioning him.
- She wouldn't.
Akeem was living
with schizophrenia.
He vanished
for a couple of months.
turned up in Timmins.
alive and unharmed.
but by then.
Hazel had already lit the match.
Accused us of ignoring
a killer in the village.
Folks got scared.
- So what's your take
on Hazel's. um.
serial killer theory?
- Omar Haddad. Yusuf Nassar.
Arjun Patel.
I've looked in all of them.
We didn't find any signs
of foul play.
- Hm. and what did you find?
- Omar had a long history
of drug use.
Arjun was a sex worker
and unhoused.
Yusuf's refugee claim
was denied.
He-he might've gone underground.
But these aren't
the kinds of guys
who leave a forwarding
address.
- No. but they are
the kind of guys
whose disappearance wouldn't
cause headlines.
and the kind of guys
who somebody could pick off
without much noise.
- Look. I walked this strip
longer than most.
I think I got a good idea
of who's out there
and who's just moved on.
Look. not every gap
in a community
is evidence of foul play.
- Yeah. you're probably right.
Still. there's just a few things
we wanna cross reference
with our investigation
in. uh. Len Marsden's murder.
- Yeah. yeah.
How about I pull my notes
and I have them sent over
to your office?
- Appreciate it.
[tense music]
- Just got off the phone
with the last of the witnesses
Webb interviewed
in the missing men's cases.
- And?
- And their statements
haven't changed.
Webb's notes line up.
I asked them about Len
and there doesn't seem
to be any connection.
[indistinct office chatter]
- We're missing something.
[inhaling sharply]
What were these men doing
when they disappeared?
- We don't really know.
Uh. Yusuf and Arjun
were last seen at intersections
and Omar was last seen leaving
his building on Dundonald.
- Did Omar live with anyone?
- Yeah. Ziggy Stardust.
His dog. Apparently. it barked
for three days straight
after Omar went missing.
the poor thing.
Neighbour called it in.
[office phone ringing]
- No. Arjun and Yusuf
were of no fixed address.
Len and Omar lived alone.
Now. that's not something
you learn about
somebody at a glance.
- The killer knew them.
Knew there wouldn't be anyone
waiting for them at home
or that there wasn't even
any home to begin with.
- Yeah.
The missing connection
is where the killer
was meeting his victims.
Learning who would
quietly disappear.
We find that place.
we find the killer's
hunting ground.
- None of the other victims
came to my bar.
There was a little cafe
over on Maitland.
Omar used to grab coffee
there sometimes.
And Arjun would get pastries
from their food rescue program
when he needed to.
- Yeah. we spoke
with the owner there.
Her statement was
in their case files.
so she said
they would come in alone.
no conversations. no company.
- What about Yusuf?
Um. any interactions
with the others?
- Yusuf kept to himself
more than most.
Moved around like he was trying
not to be seen.
Heard he was closeted.
- And facing deportation.
To someone like that.
discretion is key.
- So. where might
Yusuf have gone
if he wanted
to meet men discreetly?
- A bathhouse.
Doesn't get more discreet
than that.
Like. now.
[soft music playing in bar]
- Low lights. private rooms.
no cameras. unspoken
understanding that. uh. people
don't talk about what they see.
A bathhouse is a perfect place
for a predator
to get close to their target
without too many eyes on them.
- Yeah. sure is.
Only three bathhouses
within walking distance.
Take your pick.
- Steamhaus Baths logo.
- Yeah.
- That's the same logo
that was on Len's gym bag
in his apartment.
[echoing gavel]
[typing on keyboard]
[indistinct chatter]
- And no Len Marsden.
[chuckling]
Look. detectives.
if these men were members
of my bathhouse. I would know.
- Well. that's strange.
because Len's bank records
show he's been a member
here for years.
[suspenseful music]
Where were you
the night Len died?
- Here. We're open 24/7.
There were over a hundred guys
through here that night.
Ask any of them.
- Tevin. did you delete
Len's membership?
He's not saying no.
- Mm.
So. if you didn't have anything
to do with Len's murder.
why'd you scrub his name?
- Because I was told to.
- Told to? By whom?
- It was Officer Webb.
- What...
- Sorry?
- What does Officer Webb
have to do with this?
- When the posters
of the missing men
started going up last winter.
I realized that
they had all been here.
shortly before
they disappeared.
I caught Webb on patrol
and I told him about it.
[chuckling]
But he said
that the serial killer stuff
was all community panic.
[sighing]
- And when did Webb tell you
to wipe Len's name?
- He cornered me
at my car last night.
Told me that you might be
around asking about Len
and the others and...
that I was to stay quiet.
He said it wouldn't be
good for business.
I know what it sounds like
when a cop makes a threat.
- Damnit. I'm out.
- I'll grab more. Here.
- Hey. need a hand?
[tense music]
Well. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
- You didn't.
- So. I heard you talking
to those detectives.
So. you're back on
about that. um.
serial killer theory again.
- I didn't tell them anything
I haven't told you.
More than once.
- Just remember.
once the suits move on.
me and my team
will still be here.
looking out for folks.
- Right. Looking out.
- Is everything okay here?
- Yeah. just making sure
everyone's safe.
[tense music continues]
[elevator dinging]
- Obstructing an investigation
and intimidating a witness
are serious claims.
I'm gonna need more than
a bathhouse owner's word
before I tell Webb's superiors
that the head of their
village detail is corrupt.
- Well...
[sighing]
he might be more than that.
This came from Forester.
- "Parents say London Police
are to blame
for daughter's critical injury".
Okay. what I am looking at here?
- A few years ago.
Webb was stationed in London.
He led a botched raid
on a strip club.
arrested one Ash Perkins.
a trans woman.
During the takedown.
she was injured and. uh.
she went into a coma because
he denied her medical attention.
- I've never heard about this.
- Well. you wouldn't have
because the London Police
gave Webb the option to resign
before they opened
an investigation.
He was never charged.
His name doesn't come up
in the article
because none of this
was ever made public.
- Yeah. Until recently.
when Ash's. uh.
parents obtained new council
and are demanding answers.
- So. Webb has a history of
violence against queer persons.
Oh. my God. I don't like
where we're headed.
- Well. then. you're really
not gonna like this.
The night Len died.
the village dispatch records
show Webb was on duty.
but unavailable
until he returned his patrol car
at two to three AM.
- The entire window
of Len's death.
- Yeah.
[sighing]: Okay.
I'll make the calls.
Bring him in.
[intriguing music swelling]
- Ash Perkins was an accident.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
I didn't hurt any of those men
from the village.
- Then. why is there no record
of Tevin telling you
they all went
to the bathhouse?
- If I had to log
Tevin's statement.
my team would've had
to follow up.
It seemed like
a waste of resources.
- So?
- I made a call.
That's the job.
It's not a crime.
- Threatening a witness is.
You went back to. uh. Tevin.
To make sure he didn't
talk about Len.
Why?
- Because I knew Len
was a bathhouse patron
from patrol.
When you showed up asking
questions about the others.
it made me realize
that I overlooked
a couple of things.
And I'd already gone on record.
Public record. dismissing
the serial killer theory.
- Then. why not get out
in front of it.
Share what you knew?
- If you had uncovered
a serial killer in the village.
the public backlash would've
put too many eyes on me.
- Your London raid
would be exposed.
You'd be staring down
on a SIU investigation.
- Officer Webb. on the night
Len was killed. you were
patrolling the village.
You have three hours
unaccounted for.
Where were you?
- I got a call that night
from a friend in London.
warning me about the article.
and telling me that Ash Perkins'
parents were demanding
that my name be released.
- Well. personally.
I think it should be.
Where were you?
- I-I needed to clear my head.
I drove down to the lake.
Forgot to turn my bodycam off.
It's all on there.
[Bateman sighing]
- Earlier. you said you
overlooked a couple of things.
The bathhouse is one.
What else?
- A couple weeks back.
Len came to me to report
an assault.
- Excuse me?
- Said he was attacked
during a hook-up.
He was really angry at first.
but by the end
of the conversation.
he cooled down
and he said that
pressing charges
wasn't worth it.
- Who attacked him?
- I don't know.
I never got a name.
[intriguing music]
- Hey. Adam.
- Hey.
- Hey. shouldn't you be
laying off the gym
while your hand heals?
- The sauna helps
with the stiffness.
[phone dinging]
[grunting]
[sighing]
- Oh. my God!
- What is it?
- This is on that path
by the Ravine.
Apparently.
Roswin's husband's sister
was the one who found him.
Ugh. that poor man.
[clicking tongue]
This neighbourhood
used to be safe.
- Hey.
Webb's bodycam checks out
for the night of the murder.
but I found something else.
- What'd you got?
- Footage of Len
reporting an assault.
- Did he give a name?
- Well. he didn't
mention a name.
but he did mention getting
two coffees from Doordash
and picking them up
around seven.
so I pulled a name
from the order.
Adam Harris.
- Hm.
Beautiful wife. cute kid.
- Yeah. and an address.
In Rosedale.
- Well. it all fits.
This guy's not openly cruising.
he's discreet.
Bathhouse discreet.
- I had the same thought.
so I gave Tevin a call.
He confirmed seeing Adam
at Steamhaus.
- Okay. so.
he meets Len
at the bathhouse.
finds out Len lives alone.
they arrange to hook-up.
When they do.
Adam attacks Len.
but he gets away.
- Seems like
the kind of loose end
a serial killer
would want to tie up.
[paper rustling]
[electrical humming]
- I didn't kill him.
I was home in bed
the night Len died.
- Can anyone. uh.
back that up?
Your wife. perhaps?
- I prefer you didn't
drag Elena into this.
- Walk us through it.
What happened between
you and Len two Fridays ago?
- We grabbed a coffee.
- Mm-hmm?
- That's it.
- That's it. huh?
Well. not according to Len.
You see.
Len told an officer
that. uh. you attacked him.
- I wasn't the one who attacked
Len two weeks ago.
He attacked me!
- Okay. well.
paint me a picture.
Floor is yours.
[Bateman sighing]
- We met at the bathhouse
a while back.
Len told me that he'd been
closeted for most of his life.
Said the shame had nearly
ruined him. It was...
It was like hearing my own
thoughts out loud.
- Mm-hmm.
And did you tell Len
about your wife? Your daughter?
- No. I gave Len the same story
I always use in the village.
- And what story is that?
- That I live alone.
No family.
New to the city.
I was careful to keep that part
of my life separate
so Elena wouldn't find out.
That's...
that's why I didn't report it
when Len assaulted me
two weeks ago.
- Okay.
[clearing throat]
Then. why don't you tell us
what did happen?
- Len offered to take me
somewhere private.
To... hook up.
We ended up
in the back of his van
in some back lane.
He... told me what he liked.
That he fantasized about
danger and domination.
pushing limits.
But once we started. he just...
He changed.
- Changed?
How did he. uh.
how did he change?
- His whole face.
His eyes.
He started to choke me.
Not playfully.
Full pressure.
I couldn't breathe.
I tried to tap out.
but he wouldn't let go.
He was just...
staring at me like I wasn't even
a person anymore.
Like I was a thing.
[shakily]: I thought
I was going to die.
And...
And all I could
think about was my wife
and my daughter and...
[crying]
[heavy breathing]
And so I fought back.
Eventually. I landed a hit
and I made a run for it.
- And that's how
you hurt your hand.
[sniffles]
- Yes.
- Adam. you said Len
took you to a back lane.
Do you have any idea
where that was?
- I think it was behind
a church.
- Just got off the phone
with Minister Cade.
He said Len left his tools
in the church's shed.
- Hmm.
- I like the shed.
You know. if Len
really did attack Adam
and went to. uh.
Webb to report it
before Adam had the chance.
well. that's calculating.
Bold.
- Hmm. it's as bold as
assaulting a man
behind the church you work at.
- As bold as volunteering
to participate
in searches for men
you made disappear.
[intriguing music]
- I smell bleach.
you smell bleach?
- Yeah.
[metallic creaking]
- I don't see it.
[grunts]
- Yeah.
It's strong here.
Yeah.
Look here.
This is not screwed in.
this panel.
Now. maybe Len didn't
match the racial profiles
of the other victims.
because...
[wood creaking]
...Len wasn't a victim...
[grunting]
...to start with.
[tense music]
Trophies.
Len was the village
serial killer.
[police sirens wailing]
- Detectives.
we've uncovered multiple
partial remains.
- Any estimate on. uh.
the number of victims?
- At least three so far.
In 25 years. I've never had
a scene quite like this.
- Thanks.
[tense music]
[buzzing afar]
[door shutting]
[indistinct chatter]
[office phones ringing]
- Are those... trophies?
- Yeah. they were stashed
in a shed
at the back of the church.
Looks like Len kept something
from each of his victims.
His way to... relive the kill.
- We've confirmed six bodies
recovered from
the church grounds.
- Six.
[sighing]
You got IDs?
- Omar. Arjun.
and Yusuf came back fast.
We're still working
on the others.
- Hm. were you able
to determine what happened?
- Some of the remains
are up to three years old.
so the specifics are limited.
but in the two
most recent cases.
the findings are consistent.
Wrist and ankle binding.
Strangulation.
- Len told Adam
he fantasized about danger
by pushing men's limits in bed.
[suspenseful music]
Hey. what is it?
- Lucy said
there were six bodies.
but we've only got
five trophies.
One of them is missing.
- So. turns out
there were more victims.
I'm hearing
there were at least six.
- That bastard. Len.
got what was coming to him.
[approaching footsteps]
- Benj.
- See you tonight. Davie.
- Bye.
- Thought I told you not
to bring that stuff in here.
You can't take that outside?
- Where am I supposed to go?
Reporters are on every block
asking about Len.
- Is that my lighter? Benj.
Come on. Hand it over.
- Thank you.
Don't worry.
I'm taking it outside.
- Every major news outlet
is-is running the village
serial killer story.
They're coming for Webb.
asking how the hell
he missed the pattern.
and where the oversight
was on his unit.
- Won't be long before they're
asking about Len's killer. too.
so where are we at with that?
- Well. Len was targeting
and murdering vulnerable people
from a marginalized community.
He was showing
no signs of stopping
and no one was doing
anything about it.
The killer put a stop to that.
- That's true.
But the cops dropped the ball
isn't a legal defence
for murder.
- I know.
- Public trust
is hanging by a thread.
If we wanna restore it.
you need to bring in
Len's killer. Quickly.
- No one was doing
anything about it.
Maybe this is a vigilante thing.
Maybe somebody found out
what Len did to a loved one
and took matters
into their own hands.
- Now we're looking at friends
and family of six victims.
three of whom we haven't
even identified yet.
- Wonderful. So we're missing
half our suspect pool.
- Yeah. but there's a vigil
in the. uh. village tonight.
If somebody close to one
of our victims killed Len.
well. odds are.
they're gonna be there.
- They were loved.
They are missed
and they should've
been protected.
If you brought something
to leave tonight.
please come forward.
Thank you all for coming.
[somber music]
[sobbing]
[indistinct chatter]
[distant sirens wailing]
- Excuse me.
[intriguing music]
- What is it?
- Omar's dog.
- Ziggy Stardust.
- We're not open
for another hour.
Detectives.
What brings you here?
- We wanted to check in.
Just thinking about you.
It must've been difficult
to learn that the man
you were canvassing with
for months
was responsible for killing
the very men
you were searching for.
- Yeah. I'm still trying
to wrap my head around it.
- Anything strange
stand out about. uh.
Len's behaviour
in hindsight?
- He liked asking people
about Arjun. Yusuf. and Omar.
Too much.
I always felt uneasy about it.
- Good instincts.
Serial killers.
they often insert themselves
in the aftermaths
of their crimes
to relive the thrill
of the kill.
And one other way
they do that is. uh. trophies.
Some like to wear
their victim's jewellery.
Others carry something on them.
ID. keys. a lighter.
- Does this symbol
mean anything to you?
- No.
Never seen that before.
- When I saw it.
I immediately thought
of the lightning bolt
from David Bowie's
Ziggy Stardust era.
The same alter ego that
Omar named his dog after.
So... I got curious.
I wanted to follow up
with his neighbour
to see if she knew
what happened to his dog.
The dog that barked for days
after Omar went missing?
And she said that...
Ziggy went to Omar's sister.
Hazel.
[shaky breathing]
- That's what Omar
used to call me.
His sister.
[sighing]
Neither of us had family
to lean on.
so we looked out for each other.
It wasn't blood. but...
it was real. We chose it.
- Hazel. we spoke to your staff.
The ones who work
at the upstairs bar
and the main bar.
On the night of the drag show.
none of them saw you
after you closed Len's tab.
not until after midnight.
What happened?
[heavy breathing]
[tense music]
- Len brought
the lighter that night
because he knew
he'd be close to someone
who cared about Omar.
You.
He got a thrill out of that.
And as you said. uh.
he overdid it on the drinks.
And when you went to close out
his tab. he finally slipped up.
He pulled that lighter
out with the cash. didn't he?
- You know. I had this
lighter custom printed
for Omar's 40th birthday.
Bowie was his sobriety
inspiration.
[laughing]
He just...
He never. ever lit
a cigarette without it.
He was a...
pack a day guy.
Len rested the lighter
on the counter.
It wasn't even there
for a second.
I recognized it right away.
And then. everything just.
uh... clicked.
Len's enthusiasm when
we would go canvassing.
And the way
he would encourage me
to open up about Omar.
He'd listen. smile.
Looking back on it.
he wasn't comforting me.
He was getting some sort of
sick rise out of my grief.
But I needed to hear him say it.
So I drugged him.
I made Len one last drink.
I swiped some ketamine
from Benji.
I waited 'til he finished it.
Spilled a drink on him.
made it look like an accident.
I watched him walk
to the bathroom.
clean himself off.
That's where I confronted him.
I told him I saw the lighter.
I know you killed them.
His whole demeanour
just shifted.
Just looked me dead
in the eye and he said.
"No one will believe you."
Before I could even process it.
Len slipped away.
But he was right.
I didn't have any proof.
You know. I spent months
sounding the alarm.
Telling anybody who'd listen.
"Someone is targeting men
in the village."
Nobody cared.
Cops didn't care.
Webb didn't care.
Just kept feeding us
the same line
about no signs of foul play.
So I made a decision.
I said.
"I'll give you foul play."
You know. Len mentioned
that he
went through
the Rosedale Trail sometimes.
I knew if he died
in that ravine.
cops wouldn't be able
to ignore it.
They'd have to take it
seriously.
Bring in the real detectives.
So I staged the crime scene.
It's the only way
to get you here.
To make you look at those
missing posters
and see the pattern
and realize that. yes.
Len was a part of this.
I knew once you did.
you'd have to investigate
these cases as connected.
'Til you saw Len
for what he truly was.
- Hazel. you must've known that
once we did learn
the truth about Len.
we would still be looking
for his real killer.
You weren't afraid
that we'd find you?
[weakly]: Yeah.
[sobbing]
I was scared.
But then I thought about Omar.
And how scared he must've been.
And how I couldn't
let that happen
to another vulnerable
person from my community.
Even now.
I'd do it again.
To expose Len.
to find their bodies.
[sighing]
At least
someone's finally listening.
Serial killers
always become famous.
Infamous.
Interviews. podcasts.
books. movies.
all while their victims
become footnotes.
With Len. they're never gonna
be able to tell his story
without talking to me.
And I'm never gonna tell it
without centring every single
one of his victims.
And the cops who didn't even see
them as human enough to care.
[door opening]
[door shutting]
- Hazel Bennett.
you're under arrest
for the murder of Len Marsden.
Read her her rights outside.
[door opening]
[somber music]
[door shutting]
- That doesn't
feel like justice.
- Maybe because it's not.
[theme song]
Subtitling: difuze
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm